<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="help_page_1_title">Introduction</string>
    <string name="help_page_1">\tThe %1$s application was originally designed to help decode the 340-character Zodiac cryptogram 
        but now it also provides an ability to create custom ciphers and decode ciphers created by other users.</string>
    <string name="help_page_2_title">Decoding</string>
    <string name="help_page_2">\tTo substitute a letter for a symbol
        tap on the symbol and type the letter in the dialog. The symbol will be then automatically replaced with
        the specified letter in every place it is located in.\n\tYou can change the color of the letters in <i>%1$s</i>.</string>
    <string name="help_page_3">\tClick the <b>%1$s</b> button with the ribbon icon to remember the binding, i.e. the correspondence 
        between symbols in the cipher and letters, and create a bookmark. To create a named bookmark,
        long-press the icon. You can change default names of bookmarks in <i>%2$s</i>.\n\tYou can navigate 
        through the bookmarks on the sliding menu.\n\tTo get back to the last bookmark, click <b>%3$s</b>.\n\tTo remove
        all the letters and start from the beginning, click <b>%4$s</b>.</string>
    <string name="help_page_4">\tClick <b>%1$s</b> to show the search dialog.\n\tSearching 
        words means finding bindings that make the cipher contain these words.\n\tThere are following 
        search parameters:\n\t<i>%2$s</i> - the results must not contradict the current symbol substitution.\n\t<i>%3$s</i> - different
        symbols can be replaced by the same letter.\n\tNOTE! The search can be a very resource-consuming operation.
		It is recommended to search for phrases (without spaces) rather then for separate words.</string>
    <string name="help_page_5">\tIf you are logged in, you can check whether your solution is correct or not. To do that, 
        click %1$s on the sliding menu. If you become the first to solve the cipher, you get points as a reward. The number
        of points you get depends on the difficulty of the cipher.</string>
    <string name="help_page_3_title">Saving result as an image</string>
    <string name="help_page_6">\tYou can save the created image by clicking <b>%1$s</b> in the sliding menu.\n\tImages 
        are stored in the \"%2$s/%3$s\" folder on the memory card.</string>
    <string name="help_page_4_title">%1$s</string>
    <string name="help_page_7">\tYou can create your own cipher and find ciphers created by other people on the <i>%1$s</i>. To enter it, 
        click <b>%2$s</b> in the sliding menu.\n\tOn the <i>%1$s</i> you can view ciphers sorted by date, popularity or 
        reward. The popularity is determined by the number of people that have imported the cipher to solve it. The reward is the number of points 
        you get if you solve the cipher.\nThere is following information available for each cipher: 
        \n - Reward / Difficulty. Reward is the number of points that is given for solving the cipher. Difficulty 
        determines how difficult the cipher is. The first solver get the maximum number of points that equals to 
        the cipher difficulty. The second solver gets half the points as a reward and every next solver gets less and less
        points until the cipher is solved by the maximum number of people.
        \n - Solved / Max solved. Shows how many people have already solved the cipher and the maximum
	    number of people who can get points for solving it. The icon is green if you\'ve already solved the cipher.
	    \n - How many people are solving the cipher.
	    \n - Who was the first to solve the cipher.
        \nEvery cipher has also 
        an avatar of its author. You can click it to view the author\'s profile. You can also see the profile of the person that was the first
        to solve the cipher by clicking their name.\nTo import a cipher,
   		click <b>%3$s</b>. You can find and load imported ciphers in the <i>%4$s</i> section of the sliding menu on the 
   		main screen. To see more information about the cipher click on the cipher title on the top of the menu.\n\tIf the cipher is solved by
   		maximum number of people, you can see the solution by
   		clicking the <i>%5$s</i> button.</string>
    <string name="help_page_5_title">Creating a cipher</string>
    <string name="help_page_8">\tIf you are logged in, you can create a cipher. You can specify a title, a description and
   		a plaintext to encrypt. The cipher will then be generated using random symbols from the Zodiac cryptogram. You can regenerate 
   		the cipher until you are satisfied with the result.\n\tOnly English characters are considered in the plaintext and placed in the 
   		generated cryptogram. There are no
   		requirements regarding the difficulty of the cipher, so it is totally up to you how difficult and adequate it is.\n\tYou can see
   		the calculated difficulty of the generated cipher. The difficulty of the cipher determines how many points will be given
        to the first solver as a reward. The author gets 3/10 of the points once the cipher is solved.\nThe difficulty D is calculated this 
        way:\n\tD = S * MIN(S / P, 2), \nwhere S is the number of unique symbols in the cipher, P is the number of unique letters 
        in the plaintext.</string>
    <string name="help_page_6_title">Logging in</string>
    <string name="help_page_9">\tTo be able to create a cipher or check your solution, you need to be
            logged in. You can create a new account or log in using existing one on the <i>%1$s</i> screen. The screen can be accessed from both 
            the main screen and the <i>%2$s</i> screen.</string>
    <string name="help_page_7_title">Avatar</string>
    <string name="help_page_10">You can change your avatar on your profile screen. The avatar creating screen
        consists of a panel with face parts, a preview panel with the generated avatar and four sliders that determine
        the location and the scale of the chosen part of a face.</string>
    <string name="help_about">Created by Dmitry Akishin\nIcons by Icon8</string>
    <string name="help_about_title">About</string>
    <string name="warning_search_text">Searching for multiple words can be
        a very resource-consuming operation and the search might be stopped due to memory issues. You should use
        this option when current symbol binding is rich enough. It is also recommended to 
        search for phrases (without spaces) rather then for separate words.</string>
    <string name="help_search_text">Search parameters:\n%1$s - the results must not contradict the current
        substitution.\n%2$s - different ciphertext symbols can be replaced by the same plaintext letter.</string>
    <string name="help_search_keep_binding">The results must not contradict the current
        substitution.</string>
    <string name="help_search_homophonic">Different ciphertext symbols can be replaced
        by the same plaintext letter.</string>
    <string name="error_outofmemory_search_text">Not enough available memory to continue the search.\nTry searching for
        long phrases (without spaces) rather than for separate words.</string>
    <string name="help_cipher_generating_params">The Homophonic Substitution cipher is a substitution cipher in 
        which single plaintext letters can be replaced by any of several different ciphertext letters.\nThey are
        generally much more difficult to break than standard substitution ciphers.</string>
    <string name="help_cipher_generating_difficulty">The difficulty of the cipher determines how many points will be given
        to the first solver as a reward. The author gets 3/10 of the points once the cipher is solved.\nThe difficulty D is calculated this 
        way:\n\tD = S * MIN(S / P, %1$.0f), \nwhere S is the number of unique symbols in the cipher, P is the number of unique letters 
        in the plaintext.</string>
    <string name="help_board_difficulty_text">Difficulty/Reward - the number of points given to the first solver.\nClick
         %1$s on the menu to view users with the most points.</string>
    <string name="help_board_reward">Reward / Difficulty. Reward is the number of points that is given for solving the cipher. Difficulty 
        determines how difficult the cipher is. The first solver get the maximum number of points that equals to 
        the cipher difficulty. The second solver gets half the points as a reward and every next solver gets less and less
        points until the cipher is solved by the maximum number of people.</string>
    <string name="help_board_solved_count">Solved / Max solved. Shows how many people have already solved the cipher and the maximum
	    number of people who can get points for solving it.</string>
    <string name="help_board_solved_count_correct">The icon is green if you\'ve already solved the cipher.</string>
    <string name="help_board_solving_count">Shows how many people are solving the cipher.</string>
    <string name="help_board_first_solver">Shows who was the first to solve the cipher.</string>

</resources>